<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30_Days_of_Indie_Gaming</string>

    <string name="game1">Eternal Senia</string>
    <string name="game2">Ao Oni</string>
    <string name="game3">Mad Father</string>
    <string name="game4">Moon Leap</string>
    <string name="game5">Hades</string>
    <string name="game6">Ori and the will of the Wisps</string>
    <string name="game7">Hollow Knight</string>
    <string name="game8">Blasphemous 2</string>
    <string name="game9">Disco Elysium</string>
    <string name="game10">Stray</string>
    <string name="game11">Slay the Spire</string>
    <string name="game12">Darkest Dungeon</string>
    <string name="game13">Outer Wilds</string>
    <string name="game14">Cuphead</string>
    <string name="game15">Spiritfarer</string>
    <string name="game16">Battle Brothers</string>
    <string name="game17">Dead Cells</string>
    <string name="game18">Cult of the Lamb</string>
    <string name="game19">Return of the Obra Dinn</string>
    <string name="game20">Journey</string>
    <string name="game21">Virginia</string>
    <string name="game22">Little Nightmares</string>
    <string name="game23">A Tale of Paper</string>
    <string name="game24">Bear\'s Restaurant</string>
    <string name="game25">Superhot</string>
    <string name="game26">Risk of Rain 2</string>
    <string name="game27">Balatro</string>
    <string name="game28">Celeste</string>
    <string name="game29">Inscryption</string>
    <string name="game30">Papers Please</string>

    <string name="description_game1">Eternal Senia is a free-to-play anime-style action RPG where players control a young girl named Senia who is searching for her adopted sister and demon hunter, Magaleta. The story follows Senia as she enters the Tower of Eternity to find Magaleta, who disappeared without a trace. Gameplay involves exploring the tower, fighting enemies in a fast-paced ARPG style (rather than traditional turn-based combat), and uncovering the sisters’ history through flashbacks. :contentReference[oaicite:0]{index=0}</string>
    <string name="description_game2">Ao Oni is a Japanese indie horror-puzzle game originally made with RPG Maker. The plot centres on a group of teenagers who investigate a deserted mansion rumoured to be haunted, only to become trapped and hunted by a blue demon monster (“Ao Oni”). Gameplay blends exploration, item and key-based puzzle solving, hiding from or escaping the monster, and trying to find a way out before it catches you. :contentReference[oaicite:1]{index=1}</string>
    <string name="description_game3">Mad Father is a morbid and atmospheric horror adventure game where a young girl named Aya navigates her father’s sinister mansion at night. As she uncovers disturbing family secrets, the game blends puzzle-solving, stealth and exploration with jumpscares and a dark narrative of obsession and revelation.</string>
    <string name="description_game4">Moon Leap is a fun, whimsical indie platformer in which the player controls a small rabbit navigating through surreal stages of grassy hills, cliffs and moonscapes. With simple mechanics and expressive pixel-art, it emphasizes momentum, timing and discovery as you leap across floating platforms and explore secret paths.</string>
    <string name="description_game5">Hades is a rogue-lite dungeon-crawler from indie studio Supergiant Games in which you play as Zagreus, the rebellious son of Hades, trying to escape the Underworld. Each run you battle mythological foes, earn permanent upgrades, and gradually unravel more of the story as you grow stronger and dig deeper into Greek-myth inspired lore. :contentReference[oaicite:2]{index=2}</string>
    <string name="description_game6">Ori and the Will of the Wisps is a beautifully crafted Metroid-vania style adventure where you play as Ori, a guardian spirit, and embark on an emotionally charged journey of discovery, loss and hope. With lush hand-painted visuals, sweeping orchestral soundtrack and refined platforming mechanics, the game blends exploration, upgrades, and heartfelt story moments.</string>
    <string name="description_game7">Hollow Knight is a critically acclaimed indie action-adventure set in a vast, interconnected underground world called Hallownest. You explore caverns, ruins and ancient kingdoms, battle insectoid enemies and powerful bosses, unlock new abilities and map the land as you uncover the mysteries of the fallen civilization beneath the surface.</string>
    <string name="description_game8">Blasphemous 2 is a dark, gothic Metroid-vania sequel where you play as the Penitent One in a twisted world steeped in religious imagery and brutal combat. Explore haunting landscapes, collect relics and powers, face punishing bosses and uncover a story of penitence, guilt and redemption.</string>
    <string name="description_game9">Disco Elysium is a groundbreaking narrative-driven RPG in which you play as a cop with a unique skill system at your disposal as you investigate a murder in the decaying city of Revachol. The game emphasises deep dialogue, political and philosophical choice, character customisation and a richly written world where your actions and beliefs shape what happens. </string>
    <string name="description_game10">Stray is a third-person adventure game in which you play as a stray cat navigating a cyber-city inhabited by robots and strange creatures. With lush visuals, exploration, stealth and environmental puzzle-solving, you must find your way home, unravel mysteries and survive among the neon-lit futuristic ruins.</string>
    <string name="description_game11">Slay the Spire is a deck-building rogue-like hybrid where you choose a character, build and refine a card-based strategy, climb a spire filled with monsters, relics and branching paths, and attempt to reach the top. Each run is unique thanks to the cards and relics you encounter, making it highly replayable and strategic.</string>
    <string name="description_game12">Darkest Dungeon is a challenging gothic roguelike turn-based RPG about the psychological stresses of adventuring. You recruit, train and lead a team of flawed heroes through twisted forests, forgotten warrens and ruined crypts, battling not only monsters but stress, disease and the ever-encroaching dark. :contentReference[oaicite:3]{index=3}</string>
    <string name="description_game13">Outer Wilds is an open-world exploration mystery game set in a solar system trapped in a time-loop. You pilot a small spaceship, visit strange planets, uncover ancient secrets and piece together the events that caused the loop. Every 22 minutes the loop resets, but your knowledge carries over, making each new loop an opportunity to go further. </string>
    <string name="description_game14">Cuphead is a hand-drawn 1930s-style cartoon action run-and-gun game featuring intense boss battles, precise platforming and a distinctive art style that pays homage to vintage animation. You control Cuphead (and optionally Mugman) as you fight your way through surreal levels, collect powerful weapons and face bizarre enemies in a vibrant, challenging world.</string>
    <string name="description_game15">Spiritfarer is a cozy management-adventure game about dying, where you play as Stella, a “Spiritfarer” who ferries spirits of the deceased to the afterlife. You build and upgrade your boat, befriend spirits, cook, farm and explore islands while lifting heavy emotional themes like loss, love and letting go — all wrapped in gentle art and soothing music.</string>
    <string name="description_game16">Battle Brothers is a gritty turn-based strategy RPG where you command a mercenary company in a medieval fantasy world. Hire and train warriors, manage resources and contracts, navigate random events and quests, and try to survive long campaigns where every decision counts and casualties are permanent. </string>
    <string name="description_game17">Dead Cells is a rogue-lite, metroidvania-style action-platformer where you explore ever-changing levels, collect weapons, unlock permanent upgrades and strive to escape the prison of the soulless castle. Fast, fluid combat, challenging mechanics and replayability define the experience. </string>
    <string name="description_game18">Cult of the Lamb is a unique blend of rogue-lite action and base-building strategy in which you play as a possessed lamb saved from annihilation who must repay the favour by building a faithful following in a sinister land. Fight gods, gather followers, build your cult, keep everyone fed and loyal — and try not to get sacrificed yourself. </string>
    <string name="description_game19">Return of the Obra Dinn is a monochrome-style investigative puzzle game from the creator of Papers, Please. You play as an insurance investigator for a shipping company in the early 1800s, tasked with boarding the abandoned ship Obra Dinn, determining how each crew member died (or if they disappeared), using deduction, logic and your wits in a hauntingly minimalistic world. </string>
    <string name="description_game20">Journey is a contemplative, visually stunning adventure game where you embark as a robed figure across a vast desert toward a distant mountain. Along the way you may encounter other players, but you cannot speak — only assist through movement and musical chimes. With no spoken dialogue, the game creates a wordless emotional journey about companionship, discovery and wonder. :contentReference[oaicite:4]{index=4}</string>
    <string name="description_game21">Virginia is an experimental first-person mystery game set in 1992 Virginia, where you play as FBI agent Anne Tarver experiencing a surreal investigation in a small town. The game uses cinematic editing rather than traditional UI, and immerses you in a story of loss, motives, memories and the unseen connections between people.</string>
    <string name="description_game22">Little Nightmares is a puzzle-adventure horror game where you play as a small child, Six, who must escape the Maw, a mysterious and grotesque iron vessel inhabited by monstrous beings. Players navigate the Maw, using stealth, quick wits, and imagination to solve puzzles and avoid or evade large and terrifying residents, all while dealing with the constant, gnawing feeling of hunger. The game is known for its dark and eerie atmosphere, unique art design, and unsettling soundtrack.</string>
    <string name="description_game23">A Tale of Paper is a charming, hand-drawn puzzle adventure in which you play as Kwirk, a tiny paper character, journeying through whimsical papier-mâché-style dioramas. Solve path puzzles by rotating the tables, navigating the tiny world and discovering hidden collectibles in this imaginative indie gem.</string>
    <string name="description_game24">Bear’s Restaurant is a poignant narrative game in which you run a café for spirits of the deceased, cooking meals and listening to their stories. Through gentle gameplay and emotional vignettes you explore themes of loss, grief and memory in a beautifully soft art-style and calming atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="description_game25">Superhot is a stylish first-person shooter-puzzle hybrid where time moves only when you move. You must dodge bullets in slow-motion, plan your movements and clear levels with tactical precision. It’s a minimalist concept turned into an intense action-puzzle experience. </string>
    <string name="description_game26">Risk of Rain 2 is a frenetic 3D rogue-lite shooter where you survive on alien planets, collect powerful items, unlock characters, scale increasing difficulty over time and try to escape before the on-slaught becomes overwhelming. Every run is different thanks to randomized elements and cooperative play. </string>
    <string name="description_game27">Balatro is a roguelike social deduction game with card-based mechanics, where you play as either the Balatro or one of the masked participants in a deranged show-trial. Bluff, deduce and adapt as the roles and rules shift each round in this inventive indie title.</string>
    <string name="description_game28">Celeste is a narrative-driven 2D precision platformer in which you guide Madeline as she climbs the magical Celeste Mountain. Along the way she confronts her own inner-demons and anxiety in a touching story about self-discovery, all wrapped in expertly-crafted gameplay, pixel-art visuals and a moving soundtrack. :contentReference[oaicite:5]{index=5}</string>
    <string name="description_game29">Inscryption is a genre-blending indie game that mixes card-based strategy, escape-room puzzles and psychological horror. Trapped in a cabin playing a sinister card game, you soon discover the rules transform into something far darker and meta-aware, delivering unexpected twists and a haunting atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="description_game30">Papers, Please is an award-winning simulation-puzzle game where you assume the role of an immigration inspector in the fictional dystopian country of Arstotzka. Each day you must inspect travellers’ documents under shifting rules, deciding who to admit, who to detain and balancing your own family’s welfare. It challenges your ethics, attention to detail and resilience in a bureaucratic system. :contentReference[oaicite:6]{index=6}</string>
</resources>